Guide to the Afro-American Cultural Center at Yale Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- African American Cultural Center records, Circa 1967-2001; Accession 2005-A-002
  - House Programs and Events
    - Youth Theater Interactions, Inc., 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 379)
    - "The audiotapestry" [Play], 1976 (Box 7, Folder 380)
    - June Jordan [Poet/Columnist], 1976 (Box 7, Folder 381)
    - City Spirit Program, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 382)
    - "Wilmington 10" [Civil Rights Activists], 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 383)
    - Senior Awards [Restricted]
      - 1976-1986 (Box 7, Folder 384)
      - 1989-1998 (Box 7, Folder 385)
    - Eldridge Cleaver [Civil Rights Activist], 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 386)
    - Theater Booklets, 1976-1992 (Box 7, Folder 387)
    - Technical Assistance Grant/Proposal [Theater Consultant], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 388)
    - Carlos Fernandez Chavez [Artist], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 389)
    - Alexis Devaux [Playwright/Poet], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 390)
    - Educational Center for the Arts, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 391)
    - Afri Productions [Black Musical Theater], 1979-1986 (Box 7, Folder 392)
    - House Program Activities [Correspondence, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 393)
    - Julian Bond, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 394)
    - Theater Artists and Resumes, 1980-1986 (Box 7, Folder 395)
    - Dwight Andrews [Jazz Musician], 1980-1986 (Box 7, Folder 396)
    - AACC Monthly Events Calendars [some months]
      - 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 397 - 399)
      - 1985-1999 (Box 8, Folder 400 - 409)
    - Theatre Booklets, 1981-1990 (Box 8, Folder 410)
    - Professor Charles T. Davis Memorial, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 411)
    - House Program Activities [Correspondence], 1973-1999 (Box 8, Folder 412 - 425)
    - Black Women Writers, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 426)
    - Event Programs
      - 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 427)
      - 1983-1999 (Box 8, Folder 428)
    - Austin Wilson [Playwright], 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 429)
    - House Program Small Posters, 1984-1999 (Box 8, Folder 430)
    - Wallace Terry [Journalist/Author], 1985 (Box 8, Folder 431)
    - Event Report Information, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 432)
    - Request for Facility Use/Calender Info
      - 1985-1991 (Box 8, Folder 433 - 435)
      - 1985-1991 (Box 9, Folder 436 - 443)
    - Manning Marable [Historian/Author/Professor], 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 444)
    - Black Arts, Crafts and Book Fair Exhibition, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 445)
    - Coalition Against Apartheid/Yale Divestment Campaign, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 446)
    - Paul Hall Dancers [Receipts], 1987 (Box 9, Folder 447)
    - The Alliance, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 448)
    - AIESEC Annual Report, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 449)
    - Special Sisters Program, 1987-1999 (Box 9, Folder 450)
    - Newsletters, 1987-1993 (Box 9, Folder 451)
    - Makeba/Masekela [Singers] Concert, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 452)
    - Jesse Jackson Campaign, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 453)
    - AACC Career Conference, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 454)
    - Potential Speaker Information, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 455)
    - Toni Morrison, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 456)
    - Resident Group Meetings, 1989-1996 (Box 9, Folder 457)
    - Basketball Tournament, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 458)
    - Louis C. Young "Star your Own Black Magazine…", 1991 (Box 9, Folder 459)
    - Black Student Leadership Retreat [Wade], 1991 (Box 9, Folder 460)
    - Alaafia, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 461)
    - AACC Annual Picnic, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 462)
    - Lance Bonner Memorial Service, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 463)
    - Resident Group Officers List and Applications, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 464)
    - Honor the Source, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 465)
    - Education Talent Search, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 467)
    - First Annual Black Achievement Awards Nominee, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 468)
    - Angela Davis [Activist/Author/Professor] Empowerment 2000, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 469)
    - Long Warf Theatre, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 470)
    - Harvard-Yale Weekend [two folders], 1990-1999 (Box 9, Folder 471)
    - "In Walks Ed" [Play], 1997 (Box 9, Folder 472)
    - Ed Hamilton/Sculptor -Amistad Memorial, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 473)
    - Coalition of 100 Black Women, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 474)
    - J. Michael Howard [Artist], 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 475)
    - Black Solidarity Conference, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 476)
    - Baraka School, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 477)
  - New Haven Community Outreach Programs
    - Hillhouse Community Theater History, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 478)
    - Newspaper Clippings
      - 1967 (Box 9, Folder 479)
      - 1968 (Box 9, Folder 480)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 481)
      - 1969 (Box 9, Folder 482)
      - 1969 (Box 10, Folder 483)
    - Black Coalition of New Haven, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 484)
    - Prison Inmate Letters, 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 485)
    - Cultural Artists in Residence Program, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 486)
    - Friends of AACC, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 487)
    - CT Black and Hispanic Visual Artists Alliance, 1975-1975 (Box 10, Folder 488)
    - AACC/Bellinger Associates Benin Mask Agreement, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 489)
    - AACC/City of New Haven, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 490)
    - Community Membership List, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 491)
    - Elm Haven Coalition [Mailing List], 1984 (Box 10, Folder 492)
    - Community Outreach Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 493)
    - Commendations by New Haven Board, 1986, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 494)
    - Commendations of Alderman, 1986, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 495)
    - Dixwell Community Center, 1980-1990 (Box 10, Folder 496)
    - Summer Dance Classes [Edmonds], 1989 (Box 10, Folder 497)
    - New Haven Amistad Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 498)
    - Yale Career Services, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 499)
    - New Haven Stage Repertory Co., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 500)
    - Community Outreach Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 501)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 502)
    - Elm City Nation, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 503)
    - New Haven Initiative, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 504)
    - [K. Goff-Crews] Correspondence Community Event, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 505)
    - Urban Improvements Corps. [UIC]
      - History, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 506)
      - Administration, 1970-1980 (Box 10, Folder 507)
      - Board Meetings/Agenda/Reports, 1970-1980 (Box 10, Folder 508)
      - Events, 1970-1980 (Box 10, Folder 509)
      - Finance, 1970-1980 (Box 10, Folder 510)
      - Newsletters, 1970-1980 (Box 10, Folder 511)
      - Staffing, 1970-1980 (Box 10, Folder 512)
      - Administration Reports, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 518)
      - Board Meetings/Agendas/Reports, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 519 - 520)
      - Events, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 521)
      - Finance, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 522)
      - Finance, 1985-1990 (Box 10, Folder 523)
      - Newsletters, 1980-1987 (Box 10, Folder 524)
      - Parent Lists, 1982-1990 (Box 10, Folder 525)
      - Staffing, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 526)
      - Administration, 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 543)
      - Board Meetings/Agendas/Reports, 1990-1998 (Box 10, Folder 544)
      - Events, 1990- (Box 10, Folder 545)
      - Finance, 1990-1999 (Box 10, Folder 546)
      - Newsletters and Flyers, 1990? (Box 10, Folder 547)
      - Parents List, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 548)
      - Staffing, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 549)
  - Yale Campus and Physical Plant
    - Pre-Registration Orientation Program [PROP]
      - Correspondence, List, 1981-1987 (Box 10, Folder 557)
      - Correspondence, programs, aide applications, 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 558)
      - Aide applications, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 559)
    - Floating counselors, 1982-1987 (Box 11, Folder 560)
    - Freshman Ethnic Counselors
      - 1985-1992 (Box 11, Folder 561)
      - 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 562)
    - Afro-American Studies Program, 1972-1988 (Box 11, Folder 563)
    - Minority Affairs
      - 1974-1977 (Box 11, Folder 564)
      - 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 565)
    - Minority Student Development Project Report, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 566)
    - Misc. Student Statistics, Undated (Box 11, Folder 567)
    - Black Faculty and Staff/AACC, 1972-1995 (Box 11, Folder 568)
    - Affirmative Action, 1975, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 569)
    - Marnesba Hill Fellowship, 1983-1988 (Box 11, Folder 570)
    - Career Services, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 571)
    - Yale Policy on South Africa-Apartheid Investments, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 572)
    - Law School Racism, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 573)
    - Physical Plant - AACC Library, Undated (Box 11, Folder 574)
    - AACC Building, 1971-1991 (Box 11, Folder 575)
    - Repairs Ordered Correspondence, 1983-1989 (Box 11, Folder 576)
    - Repairs Survey Estimates, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 577)
    - Security, 1974-1986,90-1991 (Box 11, Folder 578)
  - Alumni
    - Notes on George W. Crawford, Law 1903, 197? (Box 11, Folder 579)
    - Black American Women Graduating Class, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 580)
    - Structure and By-Laws of Y4A, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 581)
    - Correspondence
      - 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 582)
      - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 583)
      - 1976 (Box 11, Folder 584)
    - Black Grad and Undergrad Student List, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 585)
    - C. Hendrick's Cartons, Circa 1980 (Box 11, Folder 586)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1982 (Box 11, Folder 587 - 589)
    - Charles Dutton/Actor, Playwright, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 590)
    - Gloria Naylor, Author, Professor, Feminist Theorist, 1983, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 591)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 593 - 594)
    - Request for Facility, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 595)
    - Correspondence and Grad. Professor Student List, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 596)
    - Black Student Roster, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 597)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 598 - 599)
    - Charles Martin/Photographer - "Passage" Exhibit, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 600)
    - Charles Martin -Letter and Photo of James Baldwin, 1989 April (Box 11, Folder 601)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 602 - 604)
    - Black Alumni Association, Conference, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 605)
    - Alumni 20th Anniversary, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 606)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 607)
    - Yale Catering Services, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 608)
    - Correspondence with other AFAM Cultural Centers, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 609)
    - Conference Panelists, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 610)
    - 25th Anniversary
      - Onaje Jackson Letter and Photo, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 611)
      - Planning Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 612)
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 613)
      - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 615)
      - SML Exhibit, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 616)
      - Panelists Resumes, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 617)
      - Oral History Project, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 618)
      - Packet, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 619)
      - Events, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 620)
    - Benjamin S. Carson [Neurosurgeon], 1996 (Box 12, Folder 621)
    - Schedule of Events and Accommodations, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 622)
    - 30th Anniversary Packet, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 623)
    - 30th Anniversary RSVP List, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 624)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Related Media, 1969-1993
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 12, Folder 626)
    - The Afro-American (Box 12, Folder 627)
    - Akili (Box 12, Folder 628)
    - Assault on Democracy in the Alabama Black Belt (Box 12, Folder 629)
    - An Alternative Press (Box 12, Folder 630)
    - Atlanta Constitution (Box 12, Folder 631)
    - AUC Digest (Box 12, Folder 632)
    - Aurora (Box 12, Folder 633)
    - Bay State Banner (Box 12, Folder 634)
    - Black Enterprise (Box 12, Folder 635)
    - Black World (Box 12, Folder 636)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education (Box 12, Folder 637)
    - Committee Against Racism National Report (Box 12, Folder 638)
    - Connecticut Afro-American Historical Society (Box 12, Folder 639)
    - Dimensions News Magazine (Box 12, Folder 640)
    - Essence Magazine (Box 12, Folder 641)
    - GRIOT (Box 12, Folder 642)
    - Guardian (Box 12, Folder 643)
    - Hartford Courant (Box 12, Folder 644)
    - Harvard Gazette (Box 12, Folder 645)
    - INCAR [International Committee Against Racism] (Box 12, Folder 646)
    - Inner City Advertiser (Box 12, Folder 647)
    - International Forum at Yale (Box 12, Folder 648)
    - Jet (Box 12, Folder 649)
    - Journal Courier (Box 12, Folder 650)
    - Libyan Arab Jamahiriya (Box 12, Folder 651)
    - Mount Holyoke Alumnae Quarter (Box 12, Folder 652)
    - Nation (Box 12, Folder 653)
    - Naylor, Gloria (Box 12, Folder 654)
    - New Education (Box 12, Folder 655)
    - New England Grapevine (Box 12, Folder 656)
    - New Haven Advocate (Box 12, Folder 657)
    - New Haven Arts (Box 12, Folder 658)
    - New Haven Independent (Box 12, Folder 659)
    - New Haven Register (Box 12, Folder 660)
    - New Journal (Box 12, Folder 661)
    - Newsweek (Box 12, Folder 662)
    - New York Daily Challenge (Box 12, Folder 663)
    - New York Times (Box 12, Folder 664)
    - New York Times Magazine (Box 12, Folder 665)
    - Yale Observer (Box 12, Folder 666)
    - Obsidian (Box 12, Folder 667)
    - People Magazine (Box 12, Folder 668)
    - Report on Free Speech and Disruption (Box 12, Folder 669)
    - Savvy (Box 12, Folder 670)
    - State of Arts (Box 12, Folder 671)
    - Teens Cool Out (Box 12, Folder 672)
    - Tennessean (Box 12, Folder 673)
    - Theater News (Box 12, Folder 674)
    - United States of ACORN (Box 12, Folder 675)
    - Village Voice (Box 12, Folder 676)
    - Wall Street Journal (Box 12, Folder 677)
    - Women In the Arts (Box 12, Folder 678)
    - WHAT (Box 12, Folder 679)
    - WYBC (Box 12, Folder 680)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine and Journal (Box 12, Folder 681)
    - Yale Daily News
      - 1999 (Box 12, Folder 682)
      - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 683)
      - 1994 (Box 12, Folder 684)
      - 1993 (Box 12, Folder 685)
      - 1991 (Box 12, Folder 686)
      - 1989 (Box 12, Folder 687)
      - 1988 (Box 12, Folder 688)
      - 1987 (Box 12, Folder 689)
      - 1986 (Box 12, Folder 690)
      - 1985 (Box 12, Folder 691)
      - 1984 (Box 12, Folder 692)
      - 1983 (Box 12, Folder 693)
      - 1982 (Box 12, Folder 694)
      - 1981 (Box 12, Folder 695)
      - 1980 (Box 12, Folder 696)
      - 1978 (Box 12, Folder 697)
      - 1977 (Box 12, Folder 698)
      - 1976 (Box 12, Folder 699)
      - 1975 (Box 12, Folder 700)
      - 1974 (Box 12, Folder 701)
      - 1969 (Box 12, Folder 702)
      - 1968 (Box 12, Folder 703)
      - 1967 (Box 12, Folder 704)
    - Yale Daily News Magazine (Box 12, Folder 705)
    - Yale Development Newsletter (Box 12, Folder 706)
    - Yale Graduate and Professional (Box 12, Folder 707)
    - Yale Herald (Box 12, Folder 708)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital, Summer 1989 (Box 12, Folder 709)
    - Yale Parents19 Newsletter (Box 12, Folder 710)
    - Yale Political Journal (Box 12, Folder 711)
    - Yale Quarterly (Box 12, Folder 712)
    - Yale Weekly Bulletin and Calendar (Box 12, Folder 713)
    - Yale University Affirmative Action Policy [varied years] (Box 12, Folder 714)
    - Yale Daily News (Box 12, Folder 715)
    - Yale Daily News Photocopies (Box 12, Folder 716)
    - Unidentified clippings (Box 12, Folder 717)
  - House Publications
    - 211 Newsletter
      - 1986-1995 (Box 13, Folder 718)
      - 1975-1985 (Box 13, Folder 719)
      - Special Alumni Edition, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 720)
      - Supplement Manuscript (Box 13, Folder 721)
      - Manuscripts (Box 13, Folder 722)
      - Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 723)
    - AACC Brochure (Box 13, Folder 724)
    - Afro-American Studies (Box 13, Folder 725)
    - Akili, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 726)
    - The Alliance -BSAY Newsletter (Box 13, Folder 727)
    - Anti-Apartheid Newsletter (Box 13, Folder 728)
    - Black Ivy, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 729)
    - Black Masks, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 730)
    - Black Tie: News of the Society, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 730a)
    - Blassingame, John W. essays. "Life and Death of Affirmative Action" and "Old Perspective on Yale's Majority House", Circa 1988 (Box 13, Folder 731)
    - Campus Conference, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 732)
    - Economic Discrimination at Yale (Box 13, Folder 733)
    - Golden Drums Black Seeds - plus Manuscript, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 734)
    - Golden Drum Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 735)
    - House Bulletin
      - 1976-1980, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 736)
      - 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 737)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 738)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 739)
      - 1974-1980 (Box 13, Folder 740)
    - Alumni (Box 13, Folder 741)
      General
      Folder is missing 2/11/2019.
    - Organization of Black Grad/Prof (Box 13, Folder 742)
    - The People's Magazine, Etc. (Box 13, Folder 743)
    - Perspectives on Black Higher Education (Box 13, Folder 744)
    - Publications Ordered by the House (Box 13, Folder 745)
    - Radia (Box 13, Folder 746)
    - Renaissance 2 (Box 13, Folder 747)
    - Renaissance 2 Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 748)
    - Ritual and Dissent (Box 13, Folder 749)
    - Ritual and Dissent Bank Statements (Box 13, Folder 750)
    - Ritual and Dissent Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 751)
    - Ritual and Dissent Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 752)
    - Ritual and Dissent Manuscript (Box 13, Folder 753)
    - RUNAWAYS (Box 13, Folder 754)
    - Say It Loud (Box 13, Folder 755)
    - Shange, Ntozake (Box 13, Folder 756)
    - Third World Voice (Box 13, Folder 757)
    - Yale Rep -Angela Bassett (Box 13, Folder 758)
  - Restricted Files (Box 14)
  - Restricted Files (Box 15)
  - Posters
    - 1970s
      - "The Present State of…"- Lecture by Prof. Derrick Bell, 1975 April 23 (Box 16)
      - Cabaret 2, 1975 April 26 (Box 16)
      - Donald Byrd and the Blackbirds in Concert, 1976 March 20 (Box 16)
      - Southern Africa: The Struggle for Nat19l Liberation, 1976 April 9-10 (Box 16)
      - Paul Robeson as "The Emperor Jones", 1976 April 18 (Box 16)
      - Black Cabaret Weekend, 1977 November 11-13 (Box 16)
      - Brothers in Brass Trumpet Duets, 1977 December 3 (Box 16)
      - Holiday Dance Benefit, 1977 December 9-10 (Box 16)
      - Putney Experience and the Yale Experience, 1977 December 12 (Box 16)
      - It's Black History Week Extravaganza, 1978 February 24 (Box 16)
      - Cabaret ‘79, 1979 November 17 (Box 16)
      - Rastafari Voices, 1979 November 12 (Box 16)
    - 1980s
      - "Killer 1999" [party], 1985 June 3 (Box 16)
      - "Spell #7" [Ntozake Shange play], 1981 April 23-26 (Box 17)
      - 20/20 [party], 1981 September 4 (Box 17)
      - Race, State and… - [Lou Kushrick lecture, 1981 October 8 (Box 17)
      - Trees and Circles - R. R. Cohen Exhibit, 1981 November 1-19 (Box 17)
      - Yale/Harvard Cabaret Weekend, 1981 November 20 (Box 17)
      - Membership Only Dinner-Buffet, 1981 December 12 (Box 17)
      - Celebration Songs - Music, Art, Jamaican, 1982 February 20 (Box 17)
      - Eldridge Cleaver: Strategies and Tactics, 1982 February 23 (Box 17)
      - Barbara Smith: Black Feminist Critic, 1982 February 23 (Box 17)
      - "Up and Around": Women's Herstory Day, 1982 March 8 (Box 17)
      - "Raisin", a Musical, 1982 April 22-25 (Box 17)
      - Evelyn Moore -Reception in Honor of, 1982 April 30 (Box 17)
      - Spring Cabaret, 1982 April 10 (Box 17)
      - Extraordinary Evening of Literature and Jazz, 1982 October 8 (Box 17)
      - "The Women of Brewster Place", Gloria Naylor book signing etc, 1982 October 15 (Box 17)
      - Halloween Party, 1982 October 30 (Box 17)
      - Nothing But A Man - film screening, 1982 February 4 (Box 17)
      - An Afro-American Cultural Celebration, 1982 February 12 (Box 17)
      - "Runaways", a Musical, 1982 August 13-22 (Box 17)
      - "In Her Own Write": Black Women Writers…, U.S. Africa, etc., 1982 April 16-18 (Box 17)
      - Past-Princeton Game Party, 1982 November 13 (Box 17)
      - "Some Call It Jazz": featuring Menage a Trois, 1982 December 3 (Box 17)
      - An Evening of Wine and Roses: Winter Cabaret, 1982 December 4 (Box 17)
      - "Shakespeare": a Concert, 1983 April 5 (Box 17)
      - A Law and Business School Colloquium, 1983 October 14 (Box 17)
      - A Medical School Colloquium, 1983 October 28 (Box 17)
      - Peter Katjavivi on: Namiban Lib Struggle, 1983 November 1 (Box 17)
      - Cabaret Weekend, 1985 June 5 (Box 17)
      - Fifteenth Anniversary, 1969-1984 (Box 17)
      - Special Presentation for Black History Month, 1984 February 17 (Box 17)
      - Black Performers/Black Composers, 1984 February 19 (Box 17)
      - "For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide…" [play], 1984 February (Box 17)
      - Rev. Jesse Jackson, Lecture, 1984 March 1 (Box 17)
      - Fifteenth Anniversary -Program o f Events, 1984 April 13-15 (Box 17)
      - "Ms Rainey's Black Bottom" [play], 1984 (Box 17)
      - Open House and Orientation for New Students, 1984 September 5 (Box 17)
      - Initial Jam of the Year Party, 1984 September 7 (Box 17)
      - The Grenadian Question: Aseklan Heard Perspective, 1984 January 23 (Box 17)
      - 10th Annual Black Community Picnic and Olympics, 1984 September 9 (Box 17)
      - "Spirits Rejoice": An Evening of Jazz, 1983 December 9 (Box 17)
      - "On Stripping Bark from Myself," Andi Chapman, 1985 May 5-10 (Box 17)
      - Gwendolyn Brooks -Speaking on 56th M.L.K. Anniversary, 1985 (Box 17)
      - Career Fair: Cross-Section of Corp. America, 1985 January 1 (Box 17)
      - AACC Introduces Season Activities, 1985 September 1 (Box 17)
      - A Medical School Colloquium, 1985 September 1 (Box 17)
      - National Coalition of Black Women…, Undated (Box 17)
      - Second Annual Awards Ceremony, 1985 October 1 (Box 17)
      - Rhapsody in Crimson and Blue: Yale/Harvard Weekend, 1985 November 1 (Box 17)
      - Life and Times of M.L.K. [Al Eaton Presents], 1986 January 1 (Box 17)
      - Black Music at the Movies, 1986 February 1 (Box 17)
      - Zamani Za Kale: Art of Njee and K. Muturi, 1986 February 1 (Box 17)
      - Dwight Andrews in Concert, 1986 April 1 (Box 17)
      - AACC Introduces Season [Activities], 1986 (Box 17)
      - Black Arts, Crafts and Book Fair, 1986 September 1 (Box 17)
      - Afri Productions: Movin19 On Up!, 1986 September 1 (Box 17)
      - Freak Fest: Halloween Dance Party, 1986 October 1 (Box 17)
      - M.L.K. Day Lecture: Alphonso Pinkney, 1987 January 1 (Box 17)
      - Dr. M.L.K. Lecture by Naomi Tutu-Seavers, 1987? (Box 17)
      - New Year's Eve Party [Club 21], 1987 January 1 (Box 17)
      - Celebrate the Dream [M.L.K Concert], 1987 November 1 (Box 17)
      - Africa Unadorned: Photo Exhibit by Norma Holt, Spring 1987 (Box 17)
      - Black History Month -Calendar of Events, 1987 February 1 (Box 17)
      - A Cross Section of Corp. America: A Spectrum of Opportunity, 1987 February 1 (Box 17)
      - Second Annual Black Arts, Crafts and Book Fair, 1987 September 1 (Box 17)
      - Down on Rumsey Street [by Denise Byrd], 1987 October 1 (Box 17)
      - Multi-Ethnic Women's Studies Seminars, 1987-1988 (Box 17)
      - Unadorned Elegance: Yale/Harvard Cabaret, 1987 November 1 (Box 17)
      - Jose Buscaglia: Forty Yrs of Sculpture, 1987 September 10 (Box 17)
      - Black Student Alliance at Yale: "Freedom…" 2 signed copies, 1987 October 11 (Box 17)
      - Poetry Reading with August Wilson [autographed], 1987 December 1 (Box 17)
      - "Spell #7" by Ntozake Shange, directed by C. Emery, 1987 April 1 (Box 17)
      - Ntozake Shange: Playwright, Poet, Author, 1987 December 1 (Box 17)
      - Call on the One [Yale Gospel Choir], 1988 November 1 (Box 17)
      - Angela Y. Davis: Women and the Struggle Against Racism, 1989 March 1 (Box 17)
      - Feminist Scholars with Degrees from Yale, 1989-1990 (Box 17)
      - Women's Studies Lecture Series, 1989-1990 (Box 17)
    - 1990s-2000s